Indiana University President's Office records, 1963-1990 C459
Indiana University Archives
- Administrative records, 1963-1990; undated (Box 1)
  - Scholarships and Financial Aids (Box 233)
    - Scholarships (Box 235)
      - Fulbright-Hays, 1971-1972 (Box 235)
      - General Motors, 1971 (Box 235)
      - Gross Scholarship, 1976 (Box 235)
      - National Merit Scholarship Corporation, 1972-1979 (Box 235)
      - From Outside Agencies (Box 235)
        - 1971-1972 (Box 235)
        - 1972-1973 (Box 235)
        - 1973-1974 (Box 235)
      - RCA, 1971 (Box 235)
      - Root-Tilden Scholarship, 1971 (Box 235)
      - Scripps-Howard Foundation, 1971 (Box 235)
      - Dennis Bland Indianapolis Star Story, 1972 (Box 235)
      - Harold and June Shane Student Aid Fund, 1971 (Box 235)
      - Marshal Wrubel Scholarship, 1972 (Box 235)
  - School of Foreign Languages Annual Report (Box 235)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 235)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 235)
  - School of Library and Information Science - Self-Study Report for Committee on Accreditation, 1984 (Box 235)
  - School of Medicine - Hospitals, 1973-1974 (Box 235)
  - Science Student Institute - High School, 1985 (Box 235)
  - Search and Screen Committee for Vice President of University Relations, 1983 (Box 235)
  - Search and Screen Procedures (Box 235)
    - 1983 (Box 235)
    - 1984 (Box 235)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 235)
    - 1986 (Box 235)
  - Search and Screen Procedures (Box 235)
    - General, 1966-1979 (Box 235)
    - Study, 1971 (Box 235)
  - Selective Service System, 1981-1983 (Box 235)
  - Seminary Square, 1976 (Box 235)
  - Senior Class Council Awards, 1971 (Box 235)
  - Servicemen's Opportunity College, 1974-1983 (Box 235)
  - Services, Contributions to the State, 1980-1981 (Box 235)
  - Sesquicentennial (Box 235)
    - General, 1971-1973 (Box 235)
    - Campaign (Box 235)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 235)
      - 1971 (Box 235)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 235)
    - Drive, 1970; (2 folders) (Box 235)
    - Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 235)
    - Fund Executive Committee, 1970 (Box 235)
    - Fund Executive Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 236)
    - Gifts (Box 236)
      - 1970 (Box 236)
      - 1971 (Box 236)
  - Sevrukas, Vaclovas L., 1976 (Box 236)
  - Sex Discrimination (Box 236)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 236)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 236)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 236)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 236)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 236)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 236)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 236)
  - Sexual Harrassment, 1981 (Box 236)
  - Seyffert, Mrs. Henrietta, 1971 (Box 236)
  - Shane, Harold G., 1972-1977 (Box 236)
  - Showboat, 1972-1973 (Box 236)
  - Shuster, Arnold, 1974 (Box 236)
  - Sister Cities International, 1987 (Box 236)
  - Small Business Development Center, 1981 (Box 236)
  - Smith, Denver, 1983 (Box 236)
  - Smith, John H., 1973 (Box 236)
  - Social Security Numbers, 1972-1973 (Box 236)
  - School of Social Service (Box 236)
    - Annual Report (Box 236)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 236)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 236)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 236)
    - Graduate School (Box 236)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 236)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 236)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 236)
  - Society for International Development (Box 236)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 236)
    - 1973 (Box 236)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 236)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 236)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 236)
  - Society of Research Administrators, 1971-1972 (Box 236)
  - Sociology, 1976-1983 (Box 236)
  - Solar Energy Task Force, 1979 (Box 236)
  - South Africa (Box 236)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 236)
    - 1979 (Box 236)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 236)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 236)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 236)
    - 1985, (2 folders) (Box 236)
    - 1986 (Box 236)
    - 1987 (Box 236)
  - Southern Illinois University (Box 236)
    - 1971-1973 (Box 236)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 236)
  - Soviet and East European Research, 1983 (Box 236)
  - Space, 1971-1972 (Box 236)
  - Spanish and Portuguese (Box 236)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 236)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 236)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 236)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 236)
  - Speakers (Outside) (Box 236)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 237)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 237)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 237)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 237)
  - Special and Charge Approval Procedures, 1974 (Box 237)
  - Speech and Hearing Center (Box 237)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 237)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 237)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 237)
  - Speech and Hearing Sciences (Department of), 1974-1975 (Box 237)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1983 (Box 237)
  - Speech and Hearing Center (Box 237)
    - General (Box 237)
      - 1966-1971 (Box 237)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 237)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 237)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 237)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 237)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 237)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 237)
    - Annual Report (Box 237)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 237)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 237)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 237)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 237)
  - St, 1971-1987 (Box 237)
  - Staff (Box 237)
    - General (Box 237)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 237)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 237)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 237)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 237)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 237)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 237)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 237)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 237)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 237)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 237)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 237)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 237)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 237)
    - Council, 1979-1980 (Box 237)
    - Job Openings, 1984 (Box 237)
    - Personnel Reports, 1984 (Box 237)
    - Retirement, 1979 (Box 237)
  - Stahr, Elvis J. (Box 237)
    - General, 1974-1983 (Box 237)
    - Senior Recognition Awards, 1972-1980 (Box 237)
  - Stamps, 1982 (Box 237)
  - Standard Oil Company/Foundation, 1971 (Box 237)
  - State Budget Agency Meetings, 1982-1989 (Box 237)
  - State Legislature, 1983-1985 (Box 237)
  - State of the University (Box 237)
    - 1977 (Box 237)
    - 1983 (Box 237)
  - State Universities Telecommunications Council, 1971-1972 (Box 237)
  - Statements of Account (Box 237)
    - Army Science and Tactics, 1970 (Box 237)
    - Citizenship Clearing House, 1970-1972 (Box 237)
    - Computer Service, 1971 (Box 237)
    - Data Systems and Services, 1970-1972 (Box 237)
    - Fiscal Counsels Office, 1971-1972 (Box 237)
    - Legislative Info Activities, 1969 (Box 237)
    - Publications, 1969-1970 (Box 237)
    - Purdue AID, 1969-1970 (Box 237)
    - Registrar, 1970-1972 (Box 237)
    - Bureau of Institutional Research (Box 237)
    - Research Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 237)
    - Safety - Suspense Fund, 1969-1972 (Box 237)
    - Standard Oil Indiana, 1969-1972 (Box 237)
    - State Tax Com - Waggaman, 1969-1971 (Box 237)
    - University Development Program, 1969 (Box 237)
    - Wisconsin AID, 1969-1970 (Box 237)
  - Statistics, 1976 (Box 237)
  - Stillman College (Box 237)
    - General (Box 237)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 237)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 237)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 237)
    - Coordinating Committee (Box 237)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 237)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 237)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 237)
  - Stockton, Rex, 1970 (Box 237)
  - Stonehenge, 1971-1972 (Box 237)
  - Central Stores (Box 237)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 237)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 238)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 238)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 238)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 238)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 238)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 238)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 238)
  - Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty (SALT) (Box 238)
    - General, 1979 (Box 238)
    - Briefing at White House, 1979 (Box 238)
  - Students (Box 238)
    - 1971-1972, (2 folders) (Box 238)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 238)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 238)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 238)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 238)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 238)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 238)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 238)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 238)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 238)
    - 1981 (Box 238)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 238)
    - 1983 (Box 238)
  - Students Advocates Office, 1986 (Box 238)
  - Family Students' Council, 1980 (Box 238)
  - Students (Box 238)
    - Ayoub, David, 1977 (Box 238)
    - Cofoid, Kent, 1977 (Box 238)
    - DeKeyrel, James, 1977 (Box 238)
    - Ewing, Mike, 1977 (Box 238)
    - Jennette, Steve (IUSA President), 1977-1978 (Box 238)
    - Schauer, Patrick J., 1977 (Box 238)
    - Schindler, Joseph I., 1975-1977 (Box 238)
  - Division of Student Affairs Annual Report (Box 238)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 238)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 238)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 238)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 238)
  - Student Appointments (Box 238)
    - General (Box 238)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 238)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 238)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 238)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 238)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 238)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 238)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 238)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 238)
    - Graduate Students, 1971-1983 (Box 238)
  - Division of Student Assistance - Special Services Programs, 1971 (Box 238)
  - Indiana University Student Association (IUSA) (Box 238)
    - General (Box 238)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 238)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 238)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 238)
      - 1977-1982 (Box 238)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 238)
      - 1983 (Box 238)
      - 1984 (Box 238)
    - Outdoor Concert, 1982 (Box 238)
  - Student Broadcast Association (Board of Directors), 1971-1972 (Box 238)
  - Student Conduct Code (Box 238)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 238)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 238)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 238)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 238)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 238)
  - Student Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 238)
  - Student Demonstrations, 1971-1972 (Box 238)
  - Students - Distribution by Field of Study and Class, 1971-1972 (Box 238)
  - Student Employment (Box 238)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 239)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 239)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 239)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 239)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 239)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 239)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 239)
  - Indiana University Student Foundation (IUSF) (Box 239)
    - General (Box 239)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 239)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 239)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 239)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 239)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 239)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 239)
    - Little 500 (Box 239)
      - 1975 (Box 239)
      - 1976 (Box 239)
      - 1977 (Box 239)
  - Student Government (Box 239)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 239)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
    - 1973-1976 (Box 239)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 239)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 239)
  - Students - Handicapped (Box 239)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 239)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
  - Student Health Center (Box 239)
    - Proposal for Fee-For-Service Charges, 1970-1973 (Box 239)
    - General (Box 239)
      - 1983 (Box 239)
      - 1984 (Box 239)
      - 1985 (Box 239)
      - 1986 (Box 239)
  - Student Health Insurance (Box 239)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 239)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
  - Student Health Service (Box 239)
    - General (Box 239)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 239)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 239)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 239)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 239)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 239)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 239)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 239)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 239)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 239)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 239)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 239)
      - 1984 (Box 239)
    - Annual Report (Box 239)
      - 1970-1971 (Box 239)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 239)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 239)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 239)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 239)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 239)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 239)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 239)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 240)
  - Student Invitations, 1979 (Box 240)
  - Student Legal Services (Box 240)
    - General (Box 240)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 240)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 240)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 240)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 240)
    - Annual Report (Box 240)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 240)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 240)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 240)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 240)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 240)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 240)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 240)
  - Student Life Study (Box 240)
    - General (Box 240)
      - 1978 (Box 240)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 240)
    - Commission, 1978 (Box 240)
  - Student Life Survey, 1977 (Box 240)
  - Student Loans (Box 240)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 240)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 240)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 240)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 240)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 240)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 240)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 240)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 240)
  - Student Loan Administration (Box 240)
    - 1979-1983 (Box 240)
    - 1983 (Box 240)
    - 1984 (Box 240)
    - 1985 (Box 240)
    - 1986 (Box 240)
    - 1987 (Box 240)
  - Student Organization Fund (Box 240)
    - General, 1967-1972 (Box 240)
    - Annual Report (Box 240)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 240)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 240)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 240)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 240)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 240)
  - Student Organizations (Box 240)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 240)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 240)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 240)
    - 1974-1976 (Box 240)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 240)
    - 1983 (Box 240)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 240)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 240)
  - Student Personnel (Box 240)
    - General (Box 240)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 241)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 241)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 241)
    - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 241)
  - Student Problems (Box 241)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 241)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 241)
    - 1972-1977 (Box 241)
    - 1975-1977 (Box 241)
    - 1978, (2 folders) (Box 241)
    - 1979, (3 folders) (Box 241)
    - 1981, (2 folders) (Box 241)
    - 1982, (3 folders) (Box 241)
    - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 241)
    - 1984 (Box 241)
    - 1985 (Box 241)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 241)
  - Student Publications (Box 241)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 241)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 241)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 241)
  - Student Records (Box 241)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 241)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 241)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 241)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 241)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 241)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 241)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 241)
  - Student Rights, 1975-1987 (Box 241)
  - Student Road Show, 1971 (Box 241)
  - Division of Student Services - Annual Report (Box 241)
    - 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 241)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 241)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 241)
  - Student Services Building (Box 241)
    - 1972 (Box 241)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 241)
  - Students as Consumers Task Forces Project, 1976-1977 (Box 241)
  - Student Visitation, 1971-1974 (Box 241)
  - Student Voting, 1971 (Box 241)
  - Substance Abuse Task Force, 1986 (Box 241)
  - Suelflow, James E., 1975 (Box 241)
  - Summer Faculty Fellowships, 1972 (Box 241)
  - Summer Sessions (Box 241)
    - General (Box 241)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 241)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 241)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 241)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 241)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 241)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 241)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 241)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 241)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 241)
    - Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 241)
  - Superconducting Supercollider, 1987 (Box 241)
  - Department of Surgery - Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 241)
  - Surplus Property, 1971-1979 (Box 241)
  - Surveys, 1980-1983 (Box 241)
  - Survey Comparison, 1970 (Box 241)
  - Survey Class of 1970, 1979 (Box 241)
  - Sutton, Joseph L., 1972 (Box 241)
  - Sympathy (Box 241)
    - General (Box 241)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 241)
      - 1976 (Box 241)
      - 1979 (Box 241)
      - 1980 (Box 241)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 241)
      - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 241)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 242)
      - 1984 (Box 242)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 242)
      - 1986-1987 (Box 242)
    - Memorial Resolutions (Box 242)
      - 1975 (Box 242)
      - 1976 (Box 242)
      - 1979 (Box 242)
      - 1985 (Box 242)
      - 1986 (Box 242)
      - 1987 (Box 242)
  - Symposiums, 1973 (Box 242)
  - System Services, 1971-1972 (Box 242)
  - System Executives of Multicampus Universities, 1979 (Box 242)
  - T (Box 242)
    - 1971-1982 (Box 242)
    - 1983 (Box 242)
    - 1984 (Box 242)
    - 1986 (Box 242)
    - 1987 (Box 242)
  - Tat, 1971-1987 (Box 242)
  - Te, 1971-1987 (Box 242)
  - Th, 1971-1987 (Box 242)
  - Te, 1971-1987 (Box 242)
  - Th, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Tho, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Thor, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Ti, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - To, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Too, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Tr, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Tri, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Tu, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Tur, 1971-1987 (Box 243)
  - Taliaferro, George, 1972-1982 (Box 243)
  - Task Force on University Organization (Box 243)
    - 1985 (Box 243)
    - 1985-1987 (Box 243)
  - Tax Legislation, 1976-1986 (Box 243)
  - Task Force on University Organization (Box 243)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 243)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 243)
    - 1973-1975 (Box 243)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 243)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 243)
  - Teacher's Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA) (Box 243)
    - Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 243)
    - College Retirement Equities Fund (CREF) (Box 243)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 243)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 243)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 243)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 243)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 244)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 244)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 244)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 244)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 244)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 244)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 244)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 244)
      - 1983 (Box 244)
      - 1983-1984, (2 folders) (Box 244)
      - 1985 (Box 244)
      - 1986 (Box 244)
      - 1987 (Box 244)
  - Teaching Films Custodians, Inc. (Box 244)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 244)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 244)
  - Teaching Resources Center (Box 244)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 244)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 244)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 244)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 244)
  - Telecommunications (Box 244)
    - General (Box 244)
      - 1980-1982 (Box 244)
      - 1982, (8 folders) (Box 244)
      - 1983, (5 folders) (Box 245)
      - 1983-1984, (2 folders) (Box 245)
      - 1984, (3 folders) (Box 245)
      - 1985, (5 folders) (Box 245)
      - 1986 (Box 245)
      - 1987, (4 folders) (Box 245)
    - Biographies of Candidates for AIECSIT Executive Director, 1982-1983 (Box 245)
  - Teleconference, 1983 (Box 245)
  - Telegrams (Box 245)
    - 1972-1976 (Box 245)
    - 1983 (Box 245)
  - Telephone Directory (Box 245)
    - 1971 (Box 245)
    - 1972 (Box 245)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 245)
  - Telephone Services (Box 245)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 245)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 245)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 245)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 246)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 246)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 246)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 246)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 246)
    - 1979 (Box 246)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 246)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 246)
    - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 246)
    - 1984, (2 folders) (Box 246)
    - 1985 (Box 246)
    - 1986 (Box 246)
    - 1987 (Box 246)
  - Telesis Corporation, 1972 (Box 246)
  - Tenri University (Box 246)
    - 1971-1975 (Box 246)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 246)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 246)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 246)
  - Terrorism (Box 246)
    - Articles, 1979 (Box 246)
    - Syllabus, undated (Box 246)
  - Testing (Box 246)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 246)
    - 1972 (Box 246)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 246)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 246)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 246)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 246)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 246)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 246)
  - Thank You Letters (Box 246)
    - 1973 (Box 246)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 246)
    - 1974 (Box 246)
    - 1983 (Box 246)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 246)
    - 1985 (Box 246)
    - 1986 (Box 246)
  - Theatre and Drama, 1972-1983 (Box 246)
  - Thomas, Charles L. – The Study of Academic Deficiencies Among IUB College Freshmen, 1975-1976 (Box 246)
  - Thu, Nguyen Xuan, 1980-1981 (Box 246)
  - Tippecanoe, 1983-1984 (Box 246)
  - Title IX (Box 246)
    - 1972 (Box 246)
    - 1974 (Box 246)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 246)
  - "Today" Show, 1975 (Box 246)
  - Tolson, George, 1981 (Box 246)
  - Trace Element Analysis Laboratory, 1977 (Box 246)
  - Trachtenberg, Mrs. Rose (Lee), 1971 (Box 246)
  - Transportation Department (Box 246)
    - General (Box 246)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 246)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 246)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 246)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 247)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 247)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 247)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 247)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 247)
    - Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 247)
  - Transportation Studies (Box 247)
    - 1969 (Box 247)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 247)
    - 1979-1984 (Box 247)
  - Travel (Box 247)
    - General (Box 247)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 247)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 247)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 247)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 247)
      - 1976 (Box 247)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 247)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 247)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 247)
      - 1979 (Box 247)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 247)
      - 1981 (Box 247)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 247)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 247)
      - 1983-1984 (Box 247)
      - 1987 (Box 247)
    - Documents, 1972-1978 (Box 247)
    - Pamphlets, etc., 1972 (Box 247)
    - Requests (Box 247)
      - 1971 (Box 247)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 247)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 247)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 247)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 247)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 247)
    - Requests and Vouchers, 1970 (Box 247)
  - Treasurer's Office (Box 247)
    - General (Box 247)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 247)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 247)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 247)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 247)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 247)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 247)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 247)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 247)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 247)
      - 1981-1982 (Box 247)
      - 1983 (Box 247)
      - 1983 (Box 247)
      - 1985 (Box 247)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 248)
      - 1986, (2 folders) (Box 248)
      - 1987 (Box 248)
    - Annual Report (Box 248)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 248)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 248)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 248)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 248)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 248)
    - Business Officers' Meetings (Box 248)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 248)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 248)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 248)
    - Business Relationships - Indiana University System (Box 248)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 248)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 248)
    - Campus Business Managers, 1978-1982 (Box 248)
    - Report of Grants and Contracts (Box 248)
      - 1975-1979 (Box 248)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 248)
    - Requisitions (Box 248)
      - 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 248)
      - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 248)
    - Staff Meetings, 1975-1981 (Box 248)
  - Treaty of Paris, 1983 (Box 248)
  - Tropical Studies, 1971-1973 (Box 249)
  - Trustees (Box 249)
    - By-Laws, 1977 (Box 249)
    - Manual, 1978 (Box 249)
  - Charles Turner vs. Indiana University, 1973 (Box 249)
  - Tyler Commencement Schedule, 1983 (Box 249)
  - Tyler Ecology Award, 1977-1984 (Box 249)
  - U (Box 249)
    - 1979 (Box 249)
    - 1983 (Box 249)
    - 1984 (Box 249)
    - 1985 (Box 249)
    - 1986 (Box 249)
    - 1987 (Box 249)
  - Ullman, Harrison (Box 249)
    - 1979-1982 (Box 249)
    - 1983 (Box 249)
    - 1984 (Box 249)
  - Un, 1971-1987 (Box 249)
  - Undergraduate Life (Box 249)
    - 1981-1983 (Box 249)
    - 1983 (Box 249)
    - 1985 (Box 249)
    - 1986 (Box 249)
  - Unionization, Employees Unions (Box 249)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 249)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 249)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 249)
  - United Fund, 1973 (Box 249)
  - United Nations (Box 249)
    - General (Box 249)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 249)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 249)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 249)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 249)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 249)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 249)
    - Delegates Visit, 1977 (Box 249)
    - University, 1975-1979 (Box 249)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 249)
  - United Negro College Fund (Box 249)
    - 1971 (Box 249)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 249)
  - United States (Box 249)
    - General (Box 249)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 249)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 249)
      - 1973-1974 (Box 249)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 249)
      - 1975-1976 (Box 249)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 249)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 249)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 249)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 249)
    - Academies Screening Committees, 1971 (Box 249)
    - Agency for International Development, 1971-1981 (Box 249)
    - Air Force Office of Scientific Research, 1971-1973 (Box 249)
    - Air Force and Air Force Academy, 1973-1982 (Box 249)
    - Army and Military Academy, 1971-1982 (Box 249)
    - Bicentennial of the American Revolution (Box 249)
      - 1971-1972 (Box 249)
      - 1971-1982 (Box 249)
      - 1975 (Box 249)